<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--Student Quotes-->
    <!-- TODO: Reminder to add Quote for 2014574407, 2014574425 -->
    <string name="quote_2014574329_miriam">Your background can\'t stop you from getting to your
        destination, be positive and never stop striving until you get there.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574330_lawrence">A man without shoes, when he sees a man without feet, he
        will thank his God, so be contended with what you have.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574331_prisca">Live while you are still living, don\'t die without
        maximizing your potentials.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574332_doris">Treat others the way you want to be treated.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574333_francess">If your action inspires others to dream more, learn more
        and do more, then you are a leader.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574335_christian">Gratitude is happiness doubled by wonder. We make a
        living by what we get, we make life by what we give.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574336_chioma">Never give up in life, once there is life, there is hope!
        We will part to meet again. Congratulations and success in all we do. Let\'s explore!
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574337_favour">God is love.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574338_kenechi">Money is not easy to get, but talent is difficult to
        develop.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574339_joshua">The secret of Godly greatness is humility, just be humble
        and beyond the skies will be your limit.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574340_chioma_rita">The key for elevation is self love, when you cherish
        your own self.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574342_makuochukwu">Love and be loved.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574343_lilian">What doesn\'t kill you, makes you stronger.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574344_collins"><i>"Nemo dat quod non habet"</i>\n When things go wrong,
        don\'t go wrong with them.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574345_obianuju">Now the real life starts.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574346_goodness">Jude 1 vs 22.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574347_ikechukwu">For I know the plans I have for you declares the Lord,
        plans to prosper you and not to harm you, plans to give you hope and a future.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574348_precious">The seeds of kindness you plant today will blossom into
        blessing for the future.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574350_charity">Strive for greatness. The time is always right to do what
        is right.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574352_kingsley">The path to genuine success is littered with obstacles,
        only those who preserve to the end become successful.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574354_augustine">Sometimes the greatest way to say something is to say
        nothing at all.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574355_judith">I can do all things through christ who strengthens
        me.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574356_onyinyechi">A single step in the right direction will pave your
        future with gold.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574361_chidiebere">Do the best you can for humanity.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574366_cynthia">Don\'t stress about the closed doors behind you, new doors
        are opening if you keep moving forward.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574357_emeka">Think, talk and live positively.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574358_kelvin">For all you do in life, put God first for he determines
        success and give victory.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574359_ndidi">Every next level of your life will demand a different you;
        don\'t wait to see the whole staircase, just take a step.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574360_blessing">Whatever you find doing, put in your best, humility
        is the key.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574363_adaobi">Be yourself.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574364_amaobi">It wasn\'t an easy journey but as usual <b>"THE LION</b>
        owns the jungle.\n Thanks.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574365_augustina">Life is a quest, conquer it.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574367_ifechukwu">All man for himself. One God for us all.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574368_chiamaka">Execute.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574369_emezie">Do more work on your character than your reputation.
        Your reputation is what people think you are while your character is who you are. Above all,
        be happy loving and be loved.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574370_gigabyte">Be a source of inspiration to people, help someone where
        you deem capable, let someone say <b>"<i>Because of you, I didn\'t give up!</i>"</b>.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574372_pauline">Wanting to be someone else is a waste of who you are, so
        be yourself.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574373_ijeoma">Don\'t chase people, be yourself, do your own thing and
        work hard. The right people, the ones who really belong in your life, will come to you and stay.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574374_onyekachi">Discipline is the bridge between goals and
        accomplishments.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574375_vanessa">Live life with diligence, decode your own epic.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574376_susan">Set your priorities right. God over everything.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574377_rosemary">Don\'t stop because you are tired but stop because you
        have finished.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574378_chukwusom">Work as if you don\'t need money. Dance as if nobody is
        watching. Love as if you never cried. Learn as if you will live forever. Just be happy.
        Appreciate what you have.\n #Dj Ozone.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574379_friday">The you in you makes you the you, you are.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574380_blessing">The world is a global village, so do to others what you
        want them to do to you.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574383_chidiogo">Not all scars show, not all wounds heal, not all illness
        can be seen, not all pain is obvious. Please remember this before you judge someone.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574384_joyce">I\'m nothing without God, He\'s still God without me.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574385_peter">Whatsoever you do for people is your worth to them.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574386_daniel">No one can motivate you until you motivate yourself.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574387_vincent">Quitters never win.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574388_chinasa">Don\'t let the person in you kill the desire in you.
        Keep burning.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574390_hope">Christ in you, the hope of glory.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574392_florence">The best way to create your future is to first create an
        opportunity.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574393_patience">White is not always light. Black is not always dark.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574395_blessing">Popularity is not a day\'s job.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574396_shalom">Whatever the activity in which you engage, do it with all
        your ability because there\'s no work, no planning, no learning and no wisdom in the next
        world where you\'re given.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574397_obumneme">Do good to people, not because they deserve it but because
        it is right.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574398_judith">Always see a positive end from the beginning.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574399_tobechukwu">There is always light at the end of the tunnel. Stay
        focused.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574400_jennifer">There\'s always room for improvement.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574401_blessing">Being yourself is the best you can be.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574402_ogechukwu">Lets learn to care and love one another without expecting
        material gifts from our loved ones. If it will help us understand human values and worth.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574403_faith">Be pretty, dress well, be prayerful and above all, be
        educated. You will always seem to stand out.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574404_kenneth">Success is when preparations meets opportunity.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574405_samuel">He who thinks doesn\'t run. He who run doesn\'t think.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574406_henry">No police No my name.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574407_maryjane">No Quote provided yet.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574408_ifeanyi">Never give up!</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574409_rita">Knowledge is like a crop, it can never be harvested if not
        cultivated. Divinity does nothing for humanity until someone prays.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574410_precious">Determination with God\'s grace leads to success. Christ
        is my solid rock.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574412_smiling">There is always another chance for everything in life,
        but the fact is that there is no chance of another life. So let us dream it, mean it, love it
        and live it.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574413_peace">Not everything that counts should be counted and not
        everything that\'s counted truly counts.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574414_emskaro">Keep pushing, keep working, keep praying till you make
        it.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574415_franca">The choices you make effect changes in your life.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574416_zuma">The forces of political monopoly and economic monopsory will
        always lead to the monotony of failure.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574417_sylvia">One with God is majority.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574419_lawrence">Just do it.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574420_jennifer">It is not an easy road, but with God it is easy. Always
        put God first in all you do in life. Be a witness, not a judge. Focus on yourself, not on
        others. Listen to your heart , not to the crowd.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574421_fortunate">It doesn\'t matter what you are or what you went through.
        God\'s eyes is open very wide and all you need is to believe that all things are possible.
        Remember history doesn\'t talk about gutters. God is the greatest!
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574422_anthony">Your imagination is your preview of life\'s coming
        attractions.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574423_perpetual">Yesterday is not ours to recover, but tomorrow is ours
        to win or lose.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574424_zikora">It all becomes clearer at the end.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574425_mishael">No Quote provided yet.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574426_vincent">Strive not to be a success, but rather to be
        a value.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574427_chiemerie">Aim higher, never settle for less.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574428_ifeanyi">Grace is all.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574429_celestina">Life is a race. Run it and run yours. Una bye bye
        abeg.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574432_chiazagom">It\'s a small world.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574434_kennedy">Do the good you can now that you can.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574435_victor">One who loves eating two eggs at a time does not know when
        he consumes a hen and a cock together.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574437_nduka">Values and virtues are not hereditary, they are learned.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014574438_gabriel">Unless you urinate on a spot it will never foam.</string>
    <string name="quote_2013474386_ebuka">My hustle moves on!!!</string>
    <string name="quote_2013474278_mary">Be beautiful, be happy. Life is too short to be unhappy.</string>
    <string name="quote_2013464162_angus">Life is my message.</string>
    <string name="quote_2013614232_victor">For we work by faith, not by sight.</string>
    <string name="quote_2013634226_maryjane">The people who don\'t study have very less things to
        think upon. Always love books.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2014574440_emmanuel">Light the world.</string>
    <string name="quote_2014464245_chisom">Always make the right decision because we live by the
        decisions we make.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_2012464169_linda">In all you do, put God first.</string>
    <string name="quote_2011474018_christian">Humility and kindness can lead to God.</string>
</resources>